Marcos Maria Pla Señorans

Full Stack Development | Software Engineer

Bella Vista - San Miguel – Buenos Aires, Argentina (+54) 9 1144727162 marcosprograma02@gmail.com <u>Linkedin</u> - <u>Github</u>

I am a full stack developer with over 6 months of project leadership experience and specialization in JavaScript and React. My skill set includes JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, React Native, Expo, Redux Toolkit, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, and Sequelize. I have been involved in all phases of project development, from designing databases to building both the backend and frontend. My experience has allowed me to develop key skills such as self-discipline, project management, and self-directed learning. My English proficiency level is B1.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

April 2023 to Present

Alpha Group Express, Remote.

- Developed a comprehensive system with three distinct views: Courier, Driver, and Seller, each tailored to their specific role's needs.
- Technology stack: JavaScript, Next.js, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Material UI.

Full Stack Web Developer - Tigger Coffee

November 2022 to December 2022

Academic project at Henry Bootcamp.

- Developed an E-commerce platform with a team using JavaScript, React, Redux, Express, and MongoDB.
- This project allowed us to work as a team, follow best practices, learn and practice GIT workflows, and utilize agile methodologies (SCRUM).
- Stack used: Frontend React, Redux; Backend Express; Database MongoDB and Mongoose.
- Repository: https://github.com/JuanSegundo7/Final_Proyect

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

October 2022 to December 2022

Academic experience at Henry Bootcamp.

- Coordinated a group of students to integrate into the study group.
- Assisted in solving exercises and promoted group collaboration (Pair Programming) to tackle challenges with JavaScript and React.

TECHNOLOGIES:

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS.
- Framework Tools: React, Next.js, Redux (Thunk and Toolkit), React Native, Expo.
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Sequelize, Mongoose, Express, Node.js.
- Tools: Slack, Material UI, Trello.
- Agile: Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical and practical coursework in 2022.
- Industrial Engineering National University of San Martin. 2021 2022.

LANGUAGES

English: B1 - Intermediate.